maxgetmore.com 2015-03-17

# PrivacyPolicy

Loylty Rewardz Mngt Pvt Ltd believes in protecting your privacy. We want to provide you with the means to control your privacy and give you a way to voice questions or concerns you may have. Information and data is collected from you to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. We use this information to design initiatives that are designed as a platform to deliver a broad range of personalized products and services to our members across a variety of different consumer brands. By knowing the preferences of our members, we can tailor-make services and special offerings for you and eliminate hassles in providing you with a superior level of convenience on a one-to-one basis. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked at various times to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. On occasions when we provide items for purchase online, we may request your card number to conclude the transaction or your mailing address to ensure proper delivery. We recognize that the value of our brands rest in our relationship with you and we strongly support the rights of our members to maintain privacy of personal data.

## These are our seven privacy principles:

**Notice:** Where we ask for your personal information, we will tell you why we need your information, what we will do with it, and what options are available to you. 

**Relevance:** We will require you to provide only those pieces of information that we need, to perform the particular service you seek from us. We collect information in different ways. We collect the domain name of visitors to our Web pages, the e-mail addresses of those visitors who volunteer them, user-specific information on the pages visitors access, and information such as survey information, postal address, telephone numbers and site registrations that you provide voluntarily. Like many other commercial websites, our websites may employ a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our site is used.

**Retention:** We will retain your information only so long as it is needed for business purposes, or as required by law. 

**Choice:** When we contact you for marketing purposes, we will let you know how to remove your name from future marketing efforts.

**Security:** We will follow generally accepted industry standards to protect your personal information during transmission and storage. We operate secure data networks protected by firewalls and passwords. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. 

**Sharing:** When we share your information with other companies to help us provide our services to you, we will require them to comply with all applicable legal requirements regarding the privacy of your information. If you are providing personal information within a registration page, it will only be used within our domain unless you choose to allow third party data sharing. Although unlikely, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to the appropriate governmental authorities. If requested as part of a legal proceeding, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation. Other companies which partner on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising or content through the use of cookies. Due to the way the Internet technically operates, we cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers or content providers if you have any questions about their use of the information they collect. 

**International Transfer:** If we send your information to one of our facilities in another country, we will protect your information with the same high level of security we employ in your home country. 

**Enforcement:** We will regularly review how we are meeting these privacy principles and provide you a means to settle complaints about our privacy practices.
